My business has grown by 30% and for a seven year old company
it sounds pretty good
but the thing about growth is that it comes with challenges.
I've realised that in order to keep growing we need more resources,
more people, more manufacturing machines,
more computer and it's scary
because it's a risk to invest money in more things
without the guarantee of a good outcome.
I thought I'd give you a little look into one of the business
decisions we made recently
because it might help you in your business too.
So in my company we only use HP
and I needed to get another HP laptop for the warehouse
because we added more stuff
but I saw that it had something called HP Advantage for small business.
I signed up because I got a members only discount of up to 25% off
and I got even more discounts if I bought more than five for my team.
Also it gave me leasing options with
which basically
means I can get the laptops I want and pay them off over 5 years.
That one decision saved me a ton of money.
If you are looking to upgrade your small business tools,
sign up to HP Advantage for Small Business.
I think it will really help.
Copilot plus Pcs, the fastest,
most intelligent Windows PCs ever.